owlpages.com 2017-08-02

# The Owl Pages - About / Contact / Copyright / Privacy

## About The Owl Pages

OwlPages.com was first uploaded on October 26th, 1998 with the aim to provide information about the Owls of the world. The site was conceived of and created by Deane Lewis. Material is compiled from various reference sources and contributions.

The Owl Pages is not affiliated with any groups, organisations or educational institutions and we do not rehabilitate owls. "Owl Pages" is a Registered Trademark and an Australian Registered Business.

## Contact The Owl Pages

If you want answers to questions, please read the Owl Frequently Asked Questions before contacting me, it might save you some time!

If you would like to stay up to date with The Owl Pages, join our [Facebook Page](http://www.facebook.com/owlpages).

Please Click here if you have found an injured or orphaned owl.

If you would like to contribute owl pictures, articles, sounds or artwork, please send them to me at the address below.

**Email Address:** deane [at] owlpages.com (you know what to do)

**Postal Address:**  
Deane Lewis  
PO Box 309  
Maryborough, QLD. 4650  
Australia.

## Copyright Notice

Most content on The Owl Pages website is subject to international copyright laws.

Students may use any content from this site for one-off school reports, projects or talks, providing usage is not displayed publicly or further published in any way.

You may use the text compiled by Deane Lewis for educational and non-commercial purposes, provided appropriate credit is given to OwlPages.com. If the text is used on a website, there must be a link to the original text at OwlPages.com.

Text and Articles not compiled by Deane Lewis may not be used without the consent of the author named near the text or article.

Photographs and video may not be used without permission from the photographer named under the full-sized version of the Photograph.

Audio files may not be used without permission from the person that recorded the sound, named near the link.

Some content is released under the Creative Commons license. Click on the "CC" near the content to see the conditions of the license.

## Privacy Statement

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [The Owl Pages ](http://www.owlpages.com/)

**Advertisers & Cookies**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

OwlPages.com is a participant in various affiliate advertising programs designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to sites including amazon.com, etsy.com, society6.com and redbubble.com.

**Registration Forms**  
Forms on this site may require users to give contact information. Contact information from the registration form is used only to send material relating to "The Owl Pages", and will not be sold to another party.

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We won't knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with us or to provide any other personal information. If you're under 13, please do not provide us with any personal information about yourself.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. **The Owl Pages** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Linking to any site does not mean that The Owl Pages endorses or recommends any product or service thereon.

**Public Forums**  
This site uses forums, and in the future, may make chat rooms, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us here.
